japantrendshop.com 2019-03-30

# Japan Trend Shop

**Privacy Policy**

Last modified: August 18th, 2010 

At Japan Trend Shop, we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Japan Trend Shop, or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post supplementary information in our article descriptions. 

**Information we collect and how we use it**

You are not required to register for an account or provide any personal information to us to browse through any Japan Trend Shop services. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information: 

* **Information you provide** – When you sign up for a Japan Trend Shop service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, such as product orders, we also request credit card or other payment account information. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Japan Trend Shop services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.   
* **Cookies** – When you visit Japan Trend Shop websites, we might send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Cookies might be important for some of our services.   
* **Google Analytics** – We use the third party service google analytics to provide us with information about visitors to our website.  
Google analytics and Double Click for publishers will store a cookie on your computer in order to provide us with this information. We use the standard google analytics report plus the?Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting feature.  
You can opt out of this reporting by google from this page: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/  
* **Log information** – When you access Japan Trend Shop sites, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.   
* **User communications** – When you send email or other communications to Japan Trend Shop, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.   
* **Affiliated sites** – We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Japan Trend Shop, in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.   
* **Other sites** – This Privacy Policy applies to Japan Trend Shop services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

Japan Trend Shop only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include: 

* Providing our services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising;   
* Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;   
* Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and   
* Developing new services. 

**Choices for personal information**

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Japan Trend Shop features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Japan Trend Shop may not be able to provide those services to you. 

**Information sharing**

Japan Trend Shop only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Japan Trend Shop in the following limited circumstances: 

* We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.   
* We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf.   
* We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Japan Trend Shop, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

If Japan Trend Shop becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. 

Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data. 

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.   
We restrict access to personal information toJapan Trend Shop, employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

**Data integrity**

Japan Trend Shop processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

**Accessing and updating personal information**

When you use Japan Trend Shop services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users’ personal information. 

**Enforcement**

Japan Trend Shop regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any further questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or Japan Trend Shop treatment of personal information by contacting us through this website. 

When we receive formal written complaints, it is Japan Trend Shop,’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Japan Trend Shop and an individual. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date. 

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site.
